zillx.com 2007-08-07

# Welcome to Zillx.com

Introduction

Your privacy is vitally important to us. We never sell, rent or lend your personal information to Third parties other Than in accordance with This policy without your consent.

This Privacy Policy focuses on describing The collection and subsequent use of your personal information. We believe you should know as much as possible about Zillx's practices, so That you can make informed decisions about your personal information.

The privacy practices of This statement apply to our services available under The domain (and subdomains) of www.zillx.com (The 'Site'). By visiting This website you agree to be bound by The terms and conditions of This Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site.

By accepting The Privacy Policy and The Terms of Use in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with This Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to The terms described in The Zillx Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance Through The act of registration.

If you have privacy questions, you may contact us.

Table of Contents

| 1. | 

Important Note About Children  
  
---|---  
2. | 

Information We Collect  
  
3. | 

Use of Your Information  
  
| 

Service Management  
  
| 

Zillx Network  
  
| 

Internal Service Providers for Our Operations  
  
| 

Advertisers  
  
| 

Events  
  
| 

Acquisition  
  
4. | 

Your Use of Other Members' Information  
  
5. | 

Email Address Privacy  
  
6. | 

Control of Your Password  
  
7. | 

Accessing, Changing and Removing Your Personal Information  
  
8. | 

Security  
  
9. | 

Notice  
  
1\. Important Note About Children.

Children (persons under The age of 18) are not eligible to use The Site.

2\. Information We Collect.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a high quality, useful and safe customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features That most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you That in our view is needed to achieve This objective.

In general, you can browse The Site without revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you opt to give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us anymore.

Manually Provided Information.

Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have The option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

We endeavor to make it apparent to you, when you provide us with information, The purpose and use of That information within The Zillx service. We design future Site enhancements to ensure The use of your data is consistent with your reason for providing it.

If you choose to message people, or post any free format textual information on The Site, we collect and keep That information. We retain This information as necessary to resolve disputes and provide customer support.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or Third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on The Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

Automatically Collected Information.

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on The Site. We use This information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and The entire Zillx network of Friend's. This information may include The URL That you just came from (whether This URL is on The Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether This URL is on The Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as 'cookies' on certain pages of The Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 'Cookies' are small files placed on your hard drive That assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features That are only available Through The use of a 'cookie'. Most cookies are 'session cookies,' meaning That They are automatically deleted from your hard drive at The end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. However ? deletion will restrict or prevent your use of some Site features.

3\. Uses of Your Information.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent or lend any of your personal information to Third parties other Than in accordance with This policy without your consent. However, The following describes some of The ways That your personal information may be used in The normal routine to provide our range of services to you.

Service Management. We use your personal information to provide The services you request. We use your personal information to: troubleshoot problems; measure consumer interest in our services, inform you about offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at The time of collection.

You agree That we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize The Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve The Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using The Site.

You agree That we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you That, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of The Site. By accepting The Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive This information. You may make changes to your email notification preferences at any time.

Zillx Friend's Network. Your Friend's can see your personal profile plus your first and last name. A person can only attain The status of your friend if you explicitly grant That person The status of friend. Your Friend's of Zillx and Friend's of Friend's of Friend's can only see your personal profile and your first name.

Internal Service Providers for Our Operations. We may use Third parties That we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of The business, product and service operations That we provide to you (e.g., search technology, email support) and Therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to These internal service providers. These internal service providers' are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions That prohibit Their use of The information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate The specific outsourced Zillx related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to Them for additional uses.

In some instances, The internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as for Zillx surveys). In These cases, you will be notified of The involvement of The internal service provider, and all additional information you provide Them and Their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, Then Their use of your personal information is governed by Their applicable privacy policy.

Advertisers. We disclose non-personally identifiable aggregated (gather up data across all member accounts) information to advertisers and other Third parties. An example of non-personally identifiable information would be 'The number of members aged 20-30'.

Events. Zillx cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other Third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and The Zillx service. Therefore, in response to a genuine request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can disclose personal information about you.

Third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information That They collect from The Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, That your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

Acquisition. It is possible That as we continue to develop our website and our business, Zillx's service and/or related assets might be acquired. Notwithstanding any provision in This policy to The contrary, in event of a merger or acquisition, your personal information may be transferred to The acquiring entity, and become subject to The acquirer's data practices.

4\. Your Use of Other Members' Information.

In order to facilitate interaction among your Zillx network of Friend's, our Site allows you controlled and limited access other members information.

By entering into our Terms of Use, you agree That, with respect to other members' personal information That you obtain Through The Site, Zillx hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: 

(a) Zillx related communications That are not unsolicited commercial messages,

(b) any other purpose That a member expressly agrees to after you tell Them The purpose you would like to use it for.

5\. Email Address Privacy.

We do not sell, rent or lend email addresses for any other purpose Than in direct association with your use of The Zillx service or as otherwise described in This privacy policy.

6\. Password Protected Access

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password. Therefore we do not recommend That you disclose your Zillx password to any Third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information. For This reason, if you know your password has been disclosed to a Third party, you are strongly advised to immediately change your password.

7\. Accessing, Changing and Removing Your Personal Information.

We offer you The ability to review and change The information you manually provide to us by signing-into The Site and entering in your new information. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once posted, in some cases you may not be able to change or remove a public posting made on The Site.

At your request, Zillx will deactivate your account and associated information from The active database. To make This request, use Zillx's cancel account feature. Information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law.

We will retain in our files some personal information to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect That all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will be deactivated from member viewing and will only be available to selected Zillx staff if needed.

8\. Security.

Your information is stored on The Site servers located in The United States (California). We use safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or Theft, as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption, 'firewall's' and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset That must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside The company.

9\. Notice.

We may amend This Privacy Policy at any time by posting The amended terms on The Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective immediately after posting on The Site. We will notify you in accordance with your Notification Preferences.
